Hizrawan Dwi Oka, Software Engineer

No. 57, Sec.2 Zhongshan Rd., Taiping Dist., Taichung, 411030, Taiwan,

Phone: +886902054922 || +6285132054922, Email: <u>Hizrawandwioka@gmail.com</u>

LINKS LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/hizrawan/

> : https://github.com/hizrawan Github

PROFILE

I am a recently graduated computer science student. Before continuing my master's studies, I had experience working as a software engineer for about three years. With the work experience and knowledge I gained while studying, it will be useful for your company in the future.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
Sep 2021 – Aug 2023	 Research Assistant at Multimedia Security Lab Design data hiding scheme for image steganography Translate the design into a Matlab program Analyze the result and create the report 	Taichung, Taiwan
Feb 2019 – Dec 2020	 Functional Developer at Fujitsu Indonesia Modify ERD according to the Subject Matter Expert's request Create function and stored procedure in PostgreSQL Create front-end function using Telerik's KendoUI framework Create back-end function using .Net core 	Jakarta, Indonesia
Jul 2017 – Oct 2017	Programmer Internship at Lapi Divusi Develop mobile attendance recording system using react native for IOS and Android	Bandung, Indonesia
EDUCATION		
Sep 2021 – Aug 2023	Master's Degree, National Chin-Yi University of Technology Major: Computer Science with 3.9 GPA	Taichung
Oct 2018 – Jan 2021	Bachelor's Degree, Bina Nusantara University Major: Computer Science with a 3.27 GPA	Jakarta
Jul 2015 – Sept 2018	Associate's Degree, Politeknik Negeri Bandung Major: Computer Science with 2.8 GPA Awards: 3 silver medals in International Choir Festival,	Bandung

Grand Prix Thailand

SKILL

• .Net Core

• C#

• JavaScript

• Python

• Matlab

• React native

• PostgreSQL

• SQL Server

• MySQL

• R

• Tableau

Microsoft Excel

COURSES

Sep 2021	Machine Learning Online Course, Stanford University Coursera
Oct 2021	Google Data Analytics Specialization Coursera
Nov 2018	Digital Business, UNPAD Kominfo's Digitalent Scolarship
Nov 2018	Cyber Security, ITB Kominfo's Digitalent Scolarship

LANGUAGES

Indonesian – Native

English – Highly Proficient (TOEIC 960)